Scientists Collection 1563-1973 Mss.509.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1563-1973; 5.0 lin. feet 10 upright boxes, 8 oversize folders.
  - Letter to Hare, E., 1877 Jul. 30; Aacassagne
  - Letter to Noble, William, 1877 Aug. 6; Birt, William Radcliffe, 1804-1881
  - Letter to Douglas, R. W., 1877 Aug. 8; Wilson, Daniel
  - Letter to Douglas, R. W., 1877 Aug. 18; Wilson, Daniel
  - Letter to Deane, Ruthven, 1877 Sep. 8; Jones, J. Matthew
  - Letter to Dent, J. C., 1877 Oct. 16; Wilson, Daniel
  - Letter to Milne-Edwards, Alphonse, 1835-1900, 1877 Oct. 26; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1877 Nov. 1; Clarke, Hyde, 1815-1895
  - Letter to Jones, L. Rupert, 1877 Nov. 5; Heyden, J. V.
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1878 Jan. 13; Button, Fred L.
    Purchased from Sessler, 8/18/1962
    Appraisal note
    FISH
  - Letter to Ekama, Cornelis, 1824-1891, 1878 Jan. 15; Lau, C.
  - Letter to Ekama, Cornelis, 1824-1891, 1878 Jan. 16; Coster, D. J.(?); Welterman, G. F.
  - Letter to Chandler, Charles, 1878 Jan. 18; Field, Cyrus W. (Cyrus West), 1819-1892; Porter, Noah, 1811-1892
  - Letter to Cooke, E. W., 1878 Mar. 8; Collingwood, C.
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1878 Apr. 17; Button, Fred L.
  - Letter to C[hristian] M[arinus] Poulsen, 1878 Jun. 4; Mörch, Otto Andreas Lowson, 1828-1878
    On same sheet as 1879 May 25 Poulsen to A. G. Wetherby.
  - Letter to Button, Fred L., 1878 Jun. 30; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Jones, Professor, 1878 Oct. 7; Montalba, Clara
  - Letter to Noble, William, 1878 Oct. 29; Birt, William Radcliffe, 1804-1881
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1878 Dec. 9; Button, Fred L.
  - Letter to Button, Fred L., 1879 Feb. 5; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1879 Feb. 15; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Hayes, Ed., 1879 Feb. 19; Dawkins, William Boyd, 1838-1929
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1879 Mar. 6; Button, Fred L.
  - Letter to Wetherby, A. G., 1879 Mar. 9; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Observatoire de Marseille, 1879 Mar. 27; Coggia, Y.
  - Letter to Nason, Henry Bradford, 1879 Apr. 13; Bolton, Henry Carrington, 1843-1903
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1879 Apr. 15; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Button, Fred L., 1879 Apr. 20; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1879 May 23; Button, Fred L.
  - Letter to Wetherby, A. G., 1879 May 25; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
    On same sheet is: Mörch to C. M. Poulsen, June 4, 1878.
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1879 Oct. 13; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1879 Nov. 13; Button, Fred L.
  - Letter to Button, Fred L., 1879 Dec. 15; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Wetherby, A. G., 1879 Dec. 23; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Memo re: Polaris narrative, 1879; Nourse, J. E. (Joseph Everett), 1819-1889
  - Letter to Ince, W. H., 1880 Feb. 2; Waterton, Edmund
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1880 Feb. 18; Button, Fred K.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1880 Feb. 24; Thiselton-Dyer, W. T.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1880 Mar. 22; Forest, M. A.
    1967-1222ms
  - Letter to Massey, Isaac, 1880 May 28; Agnew, D. Hayes
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1880 Jul. 7; Christison, Robert
  - Autograph, 1880 Oct. 2; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887
  - Autograph, 1880 Dec. 19; Helmholtz, Ellen
  - Letter to Schmidt, J. C., 1880 Dec. 30; Austin, John H.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1881 Jan. 28; Zehender, Dr.
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1881 Jan. 31; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1881 Apr. 2; Janssens, E.
  - Letter to Hayes, Isaac I., 1881 May 7; Billings, John E.
  - Letter to Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892, 1881 Jun. 3; Spencer, Herbert, 1820-1903
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1881 Jun. 27; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Hart, Ernest Abraham, 1835-1898, 1881 Aug. 6; Jacobi, A. (Abraham), 1830-1919
    Hart was editor of the British Medical Journal and Medical Record.
  - Letter to Wetherby, A. G., 1881 Sep. 12; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Bessey, Charles E. (Charles Edwin), 1845-1915, 1881 Sep. 26; Walmsley, W. H.
  - Letter to Hart, Ernest Abraham, 1835-1898, 1881 Oct. 1; Saule, Gieler
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1881 Nov. 3; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to De Bille, C. J. A., 1881 Nov. 29; Rau, Charles, 1826-1887
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1881 Dec. 10; Charles?
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1881 Dec. 26; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Milne-Edwards, Alphonse, 1835-1900, 1881; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
  - Letter to Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892, 1882 Jan. 29; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Bessey, Charles E. (Charles Edwin), 1845-1915, 1882 Jan. 31; Walmsley, W. H.
  - Letter to Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892, 1882 Feb. 1; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Thompson, R. E., 1882 Feb. 13; Shaefer, P. W.
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1882 Mar. 1; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1882 Apr. 2; Button, Fred L.
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1882 Apr. 3; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Wetherby, A. G., 1882 Apr. 30; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Wood, William Hayes, 1882 Jun. 5; Coues, Elliott, 1842-1899
  - Letter to Wetherby, A. G., 1882 Jun. 18; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Strachey, Richard, 1882 Jul. 3; Stokes, G. G.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1882 Jul. 9; Weingartner, Felix
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1882 Jul. 12; Collier, John
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1882 Aug. 22; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Carrolton, W., 1882 Aug. 29; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Brooks, J. C., 1882 Sep. 29; Morriss, Francis Orpon
  - Letter to Brooks, George, 1882 Oct. 7; Sadtler, Samuel P., (Samuel Phillip), 1847-1923
  - Letter to Thompson, R. E., 1882 Oct. 7; Sellers, Coleman
  - Letter to Button, Fred L., 1882 Nov. 23; Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-
  - Letter to Thompson, Prof., 1882 Dec. 2; Haupt, Lewis M., (Lewis Muhlenberg), b. 1844
  - Letter to Jenkins, H. M., 1883 Jun. 6; Sadtler, Samuel P., (Samuel Phillip), 1847-1923
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1883 Oct. 4; Charles?
  - Letter to Stoddart, Joseph Marshall, 1884 Jan. 5; Koenig, George Augustus
  - Letter to Evans, John, 1884 Jan. 23; Boehm, J. E.
  - Letter to Chapman, J., 1884 Jan. 30; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1884 Mar. 21; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Smith, Miss, 1884 Apr. 28:; Quain, Richard, 1816-1898
  - Prescription, 1884 Jul. 15; White-Cooper, William, 1816-1886
  - Letter to Poulsen, Christian Marinus, 1818-, 1884 Jul. 26; Wetherby, A. G.
  - Letter to Steedman, P. A., 1884 Sep. 18; Paget, James, Sir, 1814-1899
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1884 Oct. 19; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Garrison, William Lloyd, 1805-1879, 1884 Dec. 2; Bowditch, Henry I., (Henry Ingersoll), 1808-1892
  - Letter to Hayden, Dr., 1884 Dec. 21; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1885 Feb. 12; Galton, Francis, Sir, 1822-1911
  - Letter to Oppenheim, Mrs., 1885 Feb. 14; Mivart, St. George Jackson, 1827-1900
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1885 Mar. 4; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Strachey, Richard, 1885 May 12; Rayleigh, John William Strutt, Baron, 1842-1919
  - Letter to Davies, Miss, 1885 May 20; Mackenzie, Morell, 1837-1892
  - Letter to Hogan, L. H., 1885 Jun. 26; Herreshoff, Nathaniel Greene
  - Letter to Garrison, William Lloyd, 1805-1879 (Children of), 1885 Oct. 9; Bowditch, Henry I., (Henry Ingersoll), 1808-1892
  - Letter to Bowman, Miss, 1886 Feb. 10; Garrett-Anderson, Elizabeth, 1836-1917
  - Letter to Hooker, 1886 Mar. 9; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Manchester YMCA, 1886 Mar. 14; Ball, Robert S. (Robert Stawell), Sir, 1840-1913
  - Letter to Turner, A., 1886 Mar. 16; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1886 Apr. 17; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Reitzel, C. A., 1886 Jun. 12; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887
  - Letter to Leighton, C. Ellerton, 1886 Jun. 23; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1886 Jul. 21; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1886 Jul. 26; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Smith, Mrs. Newman, 1886 Aug. 2; Allman, George James
  - Address sheet to Le Metayer de Guichainville, 1886 Aug. 9; Saccardo, P.A.
  - Statement about Charles Robert Darwin, 1886 Dec. 12; Seebohm, Henry, 1832-1895
  - Letter to Fomer, F., 1886 Dec. 21; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Presentation note, 1886?; Véron, Pierre
  - Essai d'une eau, 1887 Mar. 21; Grignon, Eugène
  - Letter to Taylor, J., 1887 Mar. 27; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Hart, Dr., 1887 Apr. 5; Zerolo, Thomas
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1887 Apr. 13; Charles?
  - Letter to Turner, Lucian M., 1887 May 14; Bell, Robert
  - Letter to Thompson, Henry, 1887 May 16; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Lambert, Brooke, 1887 Jun. 6; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Peirce, C. M., 1887 Jun. 6; Bodley. Rachel L.
  - Letter to Lockyer, J. Norman, 1887 Jun. 27; Hind, John Russell
  - Letter to George, 1887 Jun. 28; Mallet, Louis
  - Examination of a powder, 1887 Jul. 7; Grignon, Eugène
  - Note, 1887 Jul. 24; Engelmann, Wilhelm, 1843-1909
  - Séance du 22 Aout 1887., 1887 Aug. 22; Suire, A.
    Animal magnetism.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1887 Sep. 5; Kekulé, E.
  - AMs Poem, Defeat...., 1887 Sep. 28; Airy, George Biddell, Sir, 1801-1892
  - Letter to Wheatley, Mr., 1888 Feb. 13; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1888 Feb. 23; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1888 May 12; Mohr, Felix
  - Letter to Lynge, Leone, 1888 May 14; Luther, S. M.
  - AMs, "Causes of the ordinary movements within the crater", 1888 Jun. 16; Oversize box; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895
  - Letter to Pruyn, Anna Parker, 1888 Jun. 22; Langley, S. P., (Samuel Pierpont), 1834-1906
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1888 Jul. 9; Luther, S. M.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1888 Jul. 24; Ormerod, Eleanor Anne, 1828-1901
  - Letter to Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892, 1888 Sep. 4; Murray, John, 1808-1892
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1888 Nov. 7; Tannery, Paul, 1843-1904
  - Letter to F.W.H., 1888 Nov. 10; Mabery, C. F.
  - Letter to Green, J. C., 1888 Dec. 14; Blodget, Lorin, 1823-1901
  - Letter to Green, J. C., 1888 Dec. 22; Blodget, Lorin, 1823-1901
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1889 Feb. 16; Tannery, Paul, 1843-1904
  - Letter to Barningham, Mr., 1889 Feb. 22; Bazalgette, Joseph William, 1819-1891
  - Letter to Bailey, James S., 1889 Mar. 29; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Rough, Walter, 1889 Apr. 1; Griffis, William Elliot
  - Letter to Green, J. C., 1889 Apr. 15; Ritchie, E. S.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1889 Jun. 3; Roper, Edward R.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1889 Jul. 28; Roper, Edward R.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1889 Aug. 4; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Pollons, 1889 Aug. 14; Hodgson, Richard
  - Letter to Manson, A. S., 1889 Sep. 15; Horsford, Eben Norton, 1818-1893
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1889 Sep. 22; Roper, Edward R.
  - Letter to Moss, Henry, 1889 Oct. 1; Ormerod, Eleanor Anne, 1828-1901
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1889 Nov. 23; Keep, Josiah
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1889 Dec. 8; Roper, Edward R.
  - Autograph, 1889; Lesseps, Ferdinand de
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1890 Jan. 4; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Harriet, 1890 Jan. 11; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Lyde, H. H., 1890 Jan. 12; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Smith, Swin, 1890 Feb. 2; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1890 Feb. 2; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1890 Feb. 8; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Posselt, H. J., 1890 Mar. 14; Rathbun, Richard
  - Letter to Hoskin, H. G., 1890 Apr. 11; Ridgway, R.
  - Letter to Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892., 1890 Oct. 20; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1890 Dec. 13; Billings, John E.
  - Letter to Cobden, Mrs., 1891 Feb. 4; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1891 Mar. 13; Cox, William Sands, 1802-1875
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1891 May 24; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1891 May 8; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1891 Aug. 11; Wells, Thomas Spencer, 1818-1897
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1891 Oct. 26; Mackenzie, Morell, 1837-1892
  - Letter to Windle, Frank, 1891 Oct. 30; B., C.
  - Letter to Turner, F., 1891 Nov. 3; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Sutton, Miss, 1891 Dec. 27; Jenner, William, Sir, 1815-1898
  - Letter to Bookman. Editor, 1892 Jan. 10; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Rough, Walter, 1892 Jun. 29; Niblack, Albert P.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1892 Nov. 8; Linde, Albert
  - Letter to Docteur, 1893 Jan. 7; Fox, Rosa
  - Letter to Lusaud, 1893 Jan. 16; Luys, Jules, 1828-1897
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1893 Jan. 18; Moreau, Armand
  - Letter to Furtado-Heine, Madame, 1893 Mar. 10; Janssen, Jules, 1824-1907
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1893 Mar. 29; Bel, Alphonse
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1893 Apr. 11; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1893 May 8; Fricke, E. H.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1893 Aug. 8; Mully, Gruneau de
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1893 Dec. 24; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1894 Feb. 27; Rayleigh, John William Strutt, Baron, 1842-1919
  - Letter to Hopkinson, John, 1894 Mar. 12; Ormerod, Eleanor Anne, 1828-1901
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1894 May 7; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1894 May 21; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908, 1894 Jun. 2; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1894 Jun. 9; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to "My dear Pollack", 1894 Jun. 13; Hunnay, David
    1975 737ms
  - Letter to Otis T. Mason, 1894 Jun. 14; Nadaillac, Jean-François-Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
    1967 2553ms
    Ref. to Mason's book Women's share in primitive culture (1894).
  - Letter to Muir, Austin(?), 1894 Jul. 8; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Swan, J. W., 1894 Oct. 29; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Hampton, 1895 May 2; Broadbent, Williain Henry
  - Letter to Green, Jesse C., 1895 May 6; Thatcher, Albert G.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1895 Jun. 4; Fayrer, Joseph, 1824-1907
  - Letter to Hart, Ernest Abraham, 1835-1898, 1895 Aug. 11; Reynolds, John Russell, 1828-1896
  - Letter to Orme, Miss, 1895 Dec. 8; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Wigeam, 1896 Mar. 26; Aldrich-Blake, Louis B.
  - Letter to Swayne, Charles Henry, 1848-, 1896 Oct. 9; Rolleston, George, 1829-1881
  - Letter to Swayne, Miss, 1896 Oct. 16; Ball, Robert S. (Robert Stawell), Sir, 1840-1913
  - Letter to Orme, Miss, 1896 Nov. 14; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Orme, Miss, 1896 Nov. 18; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Rowe, Dr., 1896 Nov. 23; Horsley, Victor, Sir, 1857-1916
  - Letter to Poulton, Prof., 1897 Feb. 4; Acland, Henry W.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1897 Feb. 24; Sargent, H. E.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1897 Jun. 25; Sargent, H. E.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1897 Sep. 14; Sargent, H. E.
  - Letter to Crellon, G. E., 1898 Oct. 21; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Kitchener, Horatio Herbert Kitchener, Earl, 1898 Nov. 18; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Ginn & Company, 1899 Feb. 8; Hill, Robert Thomas
  - Letter to Oppenheim, L., 1899 Jul. 14; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Oppenheim, L., 1900 Jan. 4; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Simpson, Mrs., 1900 Mar. 15; Galton, Francis, Sir, 1822-1911
  - Invitation to the funeral of Joseph Bertrand, 1900 Apr. 13
    Bertrand, J. (Joseph), 1822-1900
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1900 Apr. 24; Church, W. S., 1837-
  - Letter to Hough, Walter, 1900 May 19; Griffis, William Elliot
  - Letter to Rees, Mr., 1900 Sep. 21; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Loury, Miss, 1901 May 7; Stevenson, Sara Yorke
  - Letter to Rees, Mr., 1901 Jul. 24; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Boueh, Monsieur, 1901 Nov. 28; Société Astronomique de France
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1902 Mar. 6; Humperdinck, Engelbert
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1902 Nov. 24; Bruch, Max, 1838-1920
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1903 Jan. 17; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1903 Jan. 27; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1903 Feb. 6; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1903 Feb. 18; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons (Desiderata), 1903 Feb. 18; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Boghandler, Dr., 1903 Feb. 23; Lynge & Sons
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1903 Mar. 28; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1903 Apr. 7; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Drew, Mr., 1903 Apr. 16; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Dolbeschoff, Miss, 1903 May 4; Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1903 May 9; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Packard, Francis R. (Francis Randolph), 1870-1950, 1904 Jan. 7; Opie, Eugene L., (Eugene Lindsay), 1873-1971
  - Letter to Packard, Francis R. (Francis Randolph), 1870-1950, 1904 Feb. 21; Opie, Eugene L., (Eugene Lindsay), 1873-1971
  - Letter to Packard, Francis R. (Francis Randolph), 1870-1950, 1904 May 20; Opie, Eugene L., (Eugene Lindsay), 1873-1971
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1904 Jun. 11; Nadaillac, Jean François Albert du Pouget, marquis de, 1818-1904
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1904 Oct. 7; Ellis, Havelock, 1859-1939
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1905 Jan. 9; Schillings, Max von, 1868-1933
  - Letter to American Journal of the Medical Sciences. Editor, 1905 Apr. 16; O'Malley, Austin
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1905 May 8; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1905 Nov. 1; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1905 Nov. 7; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Packard, Francis R. (Francis Randolph), 1870-1950, 1905 Dec. 15; Ophüls, W.
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1906 Feb. 8; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Lynge & Sons, 1906 Mar. 27; Newton, Alfred, 1829-1907
  - Letter to Wheatley, Mr., 1906 Jun. 16; Turner, H. H.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1906 Sep. 6; Cass, Charles L.
  - Letter to Adderly, 1906 Oct. 22; Lodge, Oliver, Sir, 1851-1940
  - Letter to Rambant, Dr., 1906 Dec. 6; Herschel, William James, 1833-
  - Letter to Colley, Rev. Archdeacon, 1907 Feb. 26; Wallace, Alfred Russel, 1823-1913
  - Letter to Schweinitz, Dr., 1909 Feb. 2; Reproduction.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1909 Jul. 8; Darwin, Horace
  - Letter to Winder, John W., 1909 Jul. 9; Greely, A. W., ?
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1909 Aug. 31; Ball, Robert S. (Robert Stawell), Sir, 1840-1913
  - Autograph, 1909 Dec. 13; Nordau, Max Simon
  - Letter to Hough, Walter, 1910 Jul. 8; Pinchot, Mary E.
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1910 Sep. 13; Winchell, Horace V., (Horace Vaughn), 1865-1923
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1910 Oct. 2; Austin, M. K.
  - Letter to Warming, Prof., 1910 Oct. 12; Oliver, F. W.
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1911 Jan. 20; Winchell, Horace V., (Horace Vaughn), 1865-1923
  - Letter to Keen, William W. (William Williams), 1837-1932, 1911 Jun. 9; Reproduction.; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945
  - Letter to Fallows, Mr., 1911 Sep. 13; Pupin, Michael Idvorsky, 1858-1935
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1912 Jun. 12; Haeckel, Ernst, 1834-1919
  - Letter to Los Angeles Free Public Library, 1913 Jan. 16; Ward, C. H.
  - Letter to Funk & Wagnall's, 1913 Jan. 25; Crookes, William, 1832-1919
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1913 Feb. 13; Austin, M. K.
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1913 Mar. 18; Ryan, Everett R.
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1913 Jul. 31; Whetzel, Herbert Hice, 1877-
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1913 Jul.; Whetzel, Herbert Hice, 1877-
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1913 Sep. 2; Whetzel, Herbert Hice, 1877-
  - List of books purchased..., 1913 Sep. 2; Whetzel, Herbert Hice, 1877-
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1913 Oct. 29; Whetzel, Herbert Hice, 1877-
  - Letter to H. J. Lynge & Son, 1913 Nov. 10; Whetzel, Herbert Hice, 1877-
  - Letter to Macfarlan, Dr., 1913 Nov. 17; Packard, Francis R., (Francis Randolph), 1870-1950
  - Letter to Hough, Walter, 1914 Jul. 2; Scott, H. L.
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1915 Mar. 25; Humphreys, Walter A.
  - Letter to Wallace, Alfred Russel, 1823-1913, 1915 Jul. 14; Darwin, Francis, Sir, 1848-1925
  - Letter to Unidentified recipient, 1918 Sep. 4; Rayleigh, John William Strutt, Baron, 1842-1919
  - Letter to Heinemann, 1918 Dec. 19; Lankester, E. Ray, Sir, (Edwin Ray), 1847-1929
    1962-1973ms
  - Letter to Mr. Ross, 1920 Nov. 2; Monsarrat, K, 1872-
  - Letter to Riley, E. Mont, 1921 Jan. 28; Hammond, John Hays
  - Letter to Oliver, Joseph, 1921 Aug. 31; Wiley, Harvey Washington, 1844-1930
  - Letter to Rolleston, Humphry Davy, 1862-1944, 1922 Oct. 10; Webb, Aston
  - Letter to Kunz, George Frederick, 1923 Apr. 27; Thomson, Joseph John
  - Autograph, 1923 May 29; Goethals, George W., (George Washington), 1858-1928
  - Certification, 1924 Mar. 18; Oversize box; Laboratoire d'Essaies des Substances Radioactives.
  - Letter to Weaver, J. E., 1924 Dec. 13; Skene, Macgregor
  - Letter to Vesper, F. Bernard, Jr., 1925 Feb. 3; Lodge, Oliver, Sir, 1851-1940
  - Letter to Lynge, Herman Henrik Julius, 1822-1897, 1925 Feb. 25; Aldrich, J. M.
  - Certification, 1925 Mar. 3; Oversize box; Laboratoire d'Essaies des Substances Radioactives.
  - Report, 1925 May 11; Glew, F. Harrison
  - Certification, 1925 Jul. 13; Oversize box; National Physical Laboratories, Teddington, Eng..
  - Letter to Keen, William W. (William Williams), 1837-1932, 1925 Oct. 22; Cannon, Walter B., (Walter Bradford), 1871-1945
  - Certification, 1925 Nov. 21; Oversize box; Laboratoire d'Essaies des Substances Radioactives.
  - Certification, 1925 Nov. 30; Oversize box; Laboratoire d'Essaies des Substances Radioactives.
  - Certification, 1925 Dec. 14; Oversize box; Laboratoire d'Essaies des Substances Radioactives.